Ghost!
The ghost is back!
Cousin.
It's me.
Don't move. Just lie still.
You had quite a scare
at my house yesterday.
I came specifically to see you.
I haven't been busy lately.
Cousin.
You don't have a fever, do you?
Your dad only cares about Cousin Tianting.
He's almost forgotten
that in this family,
there is a
smart and capable
second young master like you.
Even though your mother is the legal wife,
this distinction of birthright
is just too unfair to you.
I...
I'm a concubine's son.
How...
How could I compare to my brother?
But I think you're much better
than your brother.
Really.
It's just a pity
that the Qi family's estate
will belong to your brother.
Even I will belong to your brother.
Mother.
Mother!
Mother, listen to this.
I've already fooled that idiot Qi Tiankun.
In a bit, I'll go cry to cousin Tianting.
I'll tell him
that my cousin has designs on me.
As long as I turn the two brothers
against each other,
the Qi family will eventually
be in our grasp.
Mother...
Mother?
Mother!
Ling Yu...
Hurry up and leave.
Stay away
from the Sheng family.
Ling Yu, are you in here?
Ling Yu!
I have something to tell you.
Ling Yu
Zhang Tianyou.
For over twenty years in the Sheng family,
every few years,
someone dies at night for no reason.
Zhang Tianyou,
what am I supposed to do?
Since your parents entrusted you to me,
I'll definitely keep you safe.
Zhang Tianyou,
I'll do whatever you say.
Why don't we go down and take a look?
Zhang Tianyou, what are you doing?
Mouse,
take her down for a look.
Tianting.
Tonight's operation is called Nest Raid.
Dad believes in you.
Don't worry, Dad.
Just watch me.
Remember!
Kill the live-in son-in-law,
snatch the treasure!
As for tonight,
only heaven, earth, you, and Dad will know.
No one else can ever find out.
Dad, I don't need to snatch Ling Yu.
We're childhood sweethearts.
She listens to whatever I say.
This is basically...
All right, all right, all right!
Son, that Earth Vein
Incantation Scripture,
that Scripture is the real treasure, okay?
Then, should Qi Tiankun come along?
How can you be so stupid?
Son, you are the genuine article.
Tiankun is a freebie at best.
In the future,
the entire Qi family will be yours.
All mine.
I understand, Dad.
Kill the live-in son-in-law,
snatch the treasure!
Yeah!
Why didn't my dad tell me
there was a place like this?
It's fine, it's fine.
Sir, look.
Why did the fire turn green?
Don't touch it!
This is a Corpse Lamp.
It's corpse oil mixed with rare minerals.
It emits a hallucinogenic scent when lit.
Don't touch anything in here!
If you touch it, we might end up
just like him...
...stuck here forever to point the way.
Hold this in your mouth.
What just happened to me?
You almost met your maker again.
Tianyou.
The path is in the painting.
Look.
Life.
Death.
Wait a minute.
The path ghosts take...
how could it be the path to life?
Then... that's...
Life through death.
The path to life is right here!
Zhang Tianyou!
How is there a place like this underground?
Looks like the Sheng family's
underground ancestral hall.
This incantation scripture
records methods to suppress corpses
and ward off evil.
Could it be that
my father's death
was due to some unknown cause?
That's right.
I found out that
it wasn't just The Four Great Families
who surveyed the terrain back then,
but also the Zhang family
of the Dragon-Seeking Lineage.
The Dragon-Seeking Zhang family?
Didn't their bloodline die out long ago?
It's precisely because their
Dragon-Seeking Formula was lost long ago
that we went through so much trouble
to find the cave-locating treasure,
the Dragon-Seeking Ruler.
You were right just now.
But back then, only
The Four Great Families left the chamber.
Patriarch Zhang of the
Dragon-Seeking Lineage and his clan
all inexplicably vanished into thin air.
It seems returning to that old chamber
to figure everything out
will still take some effort.